{
    "1": {
        "question" : "What game is the most sold ?",
        "aswers" : [
            "1. Minecraft", 
            "2. GTA V",
            "3. Tetris", 
            "4. Super Mario Bros"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "1. Minecraft"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "Which of thoese applications isn't a social network ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Facebook", 
            "2. Uber", 
            "3. Tinder", 
            "4. Instagram"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "2. Uber"
    },
    "3": {
        "question": " What is HTML ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Programming Language",
            "2. Hit Text Markup Language",
            "3. Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "4. Hyper Theme Markup Language"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "3. Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    "4": {
        "question": " Which of those frameworks don't belong a JavaScript ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Vue",
            "2. React",
            "3. Angular",
            "4. Django"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "4. Django"
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "What is CSS ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Cascading Style Sheets",
            "2. Cascading Style Style",
            "3. Cascading Style Shell",
            "4. Custom Style Sheets"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "1. Cascading Style Sheets"
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "Which of those languages ​​isn't a programming language ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Java",
            "2. Python",
            "3. HTML",
            "4. Rubi"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "3. HTML"
    },
    "7": {
        "question": " What cryptocurrency is the most popular ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Bitcoin",
            "2. Dogecoin",
            "3. Tether",
            "4. ethereum"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "1. Bitcoin"
    },
    "8": {
        "question": " What is an AI ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Artificial Intelligence",
            "2. Art Illuminated",
            "3. Artificial Index",
            "4. Programming Language"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "1. Artificial Intelligence"
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "Which of those companies is electric cars ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Uber",
            "2. Mercado Libre",
            "3. Tesla",
            "4. Rappi"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "3. Tesla"
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "Which of those animals cann't be a pet ?",
        "aswers": [
            "1. Dog",
            "2. Cat",
            "3. Fish",
            "4. Lion"
        ],
        "aswerCorrect": "4. Lion"
    }
}